No one escapes the daily grind.
American Carnage is a mystery, thriller, comedy film directed by Diego Hallivis.
After a governor issues an executive order to arrest the children of undocumented immigrants, the detained youth are
offered an opportunity to have their charges dropped by volunteering to provide care to the elderly.
Once inside the elder care facility, however, they discover more
twisted secrets than they could have possibly imagined.
JP, played by Jorge Lendeborg Jr..
Camila, played by Jenna Ortega.
Big Mac, played by Allen Maldonado.
Lily, played by Yumarie Morales.
Chris, played by Jorge Diaz.
Micah, played by Bella Wholey Ortiz.
American Carnage is a 2022 American comedy horror film written by Diego Hallivis and Julio Hallivis,
directed by Diego Hallivis and starring Jorge Lendeborg Jr., Jenna Ortega and Eric Dane.
The film has a political message in favor of immigrant rights and takes its
name from a line from Donald Trump's first inaugural speech.
The film explores themes of sentence, illegal immigration,
aging, senior citizen, retirement community.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.